So, of course, the regular meat and the livestock gentlemen, for March 15, 2021, over
two of the proclamation, the clearing March 15 to the 21st, 2021, is rain,
where this week, the city of Wyoming, a lot of the county of Oklahoma, top above of Wyoming,
is one of our three-hundred-bought clubs, one of the three-hundred clubs, top of the international,
a global organization of leaders, working together to improve the quality of lives and local communities
throughout the world. Whereas, pop, their national scope is on service to people affected by granulated disorders
of the 1990s. Since then, across the 25,000-thousand members of the working together
to increase awareness and race funds, the program associated with this focus,
and whereas, pilot, their national provides guidance and encouragement to our communities
to sponsorship of activities which increase public awareness of advances and benefits of brain research.
And whereas, pilot and national awards, grants and scholarships,
support and students pursuing vocation and to rank health and safety.
And whereas, pilot clubs are joining others for bringing awareness week to provide information
about diseases affected, affecting one hundred fifty million adults and children.
This international effort includes hospitals, schools, government agencies, and community groups working together
to expand the interest and brain research and brain related disorders.
Now, therefore, we've resolved that my partner in Wyoming said,
do your part, declare March 15 to 21, the brain awareness week within the city of Wyoming
and in November. So, being motion to approve the appointment, I think he said,
I have a question for you.
Second, I have a question for you.
Five, number three, population, planning, April 2021, as World Autism Month,
and April 2nd, 2021, and World Autism Awareness Day.
And, first of all, for name it.
I'm also going to direct other projects that are non-related to this topic tonight.
It's my pleasure to be here tonight and to just have autism bridge with you.
One of the 54 individuals in the United States and the world has the diagnosis of autism.
Autism is in our problem, it's work.
And what that means is that there are differences that we have the individual perceive a world
and we have the individual perceive a world and we have a war behind us.
And you might think about the names you might see in the movies,
portray the sub-autumn, you know, certainly the individuals who might see that
have started in a lot of ways.
And a lot of the disabilities are different, but autism.
Sometimes they do have them together.
But typically, what happens with autism is their individual.
Is there a lot of a wide spectrum of sensory issues,
a perception for rallying?
A perception of, yes, I want to tell you, tense and the way to pay to understand
another perspective or the over and the leg.
And so, there are so many individuals in the world that are impacted by this,
and so I'm honored that you're able to stand with those individuals.
I serve on the number of parents and four groups, and I will say that there are a lot of people who are trying to
you're safe.
And so, thank you.
I'm going to start with a little bit of the hair right now, and I've heard originally how
the war is.
And so, I'm just sharing that with them.
I thought I thought you're here to be able to analyze, and I'm going to be sitting
in my army.
So, it's an interesting topic.
A lot of times, the impact range of conditions was well,
typically we'll have to know which ones we're building.
They think how, other type of who's there, which one we're trying to say,
what kind of disability or the learning differences.
And individuals with autism, how are they easy to get somebody to be balanced.
And I've heard to you in this room right now, more than just myself,
there's somebody in my family, but I don't know.
So, thank you.
Do you have any questions for me?
Well, I can tell you, you're 100% correct.
There is somebody you're affected by that.
Because my grandson is autistic.
And so, I'm going to want to go against this.
Of course, we have a question, but you're right.
There's a lot of kids in our school system that they're all inspector.
And they have a lot of difficulties.
And I think we need to bring words to that, because sometimes people just don't know how to handle it.
The view of it is, if we both have their strengths and their talents,
we would see that the uniqueness of their strengths that they want,
and there are so many strengths that they have that are traditional.
And if we're always looking at the world through what we expect,
instead of what could be.
And so, if we can have a more inclusive society, other different things,
we would show us how to be at the world in terms of technology and advancements.
Just humanity.
Thank you.
I'll read the motion.
I said I did the last one, and the first one,
how many of you have done.
For 2021, we're all all doesn't work.
The next ratio of, is month of March.
2020, we're all all doesn't,
the learnedness of where to today, and we're all off
just a month, and we're sitting at my home,
at County of The Home.
But as often, we'll pause as we'll fix,
One, the 54 children and one, the 45 adults, as a complex disorder that affects each person
definitely, resulting in unique strengths and challenges, whereas autism can cause challenges
with verbal, unbearable communication, social interaction, that repetitive behaviors make it
effective in one, regardless of age, race, ethnicity, gender, or social economic background,
and whereas autism is often accompanied by medical conditions that affect the plot of life,
whereas they comprehensive collaborative approach will help in banks research, providing
better understanding of many forms of autism while strengthening advocacy, efforts
in ensuring access to services and resources to develop the life span.
Whereas early diagnosis and intervention tend to individual needs in that plot long benefits,
each in transition to childhood to fostering greater independence.
And whereas each person, family, affecting autism, should have access to reliable information,
supports and opportunities to live up to their greatest potential.
And whereas the city of Miami is honored to take part in the annual observing
of the role of autism on a role of autism artist day to address the diverse needs
of individual and families affected by autism.
Now, for now, therefore, we resolve the matter of partnering with my city council,
due to your body, recognizing, well, 2021 is role of autism on an equal second to 2021.
There's a role of autism on the various day with the city of Miami that increase understanding
acceptance of a big role of autism spectrum disorder.
Thank you.
For the floor, we're about to give up and unskilled personal parents.
We're at any of the next.
For five, the significant staff request, we approve our six programs.
I'm not sure if you need any time to talk about it.
Thank you.
question?
I just, okay, can you just, can you just, can you write on ink computer explaining what
the little bit of like.
Well, the kind of fragmented, what's the source of the administration's reporting?
It's been both benefiting and 80% have it spread, that it will grow and then hit a million
percent of it comes from the state, the special funding for the state.
And so we have to apply for it over here and then, or award this funding, you know, all
else goes a lot higher than a 4th grade.
And then we're kind of in a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a.
And then the other questions?
I mean, they make, they make one, they're proof and sit.
Did you know, except the.
Perfect.
All right.
Good.
advisory board, to approve the memorandum of understanding with the all-local and
problem market, just the program.
Thank you, thank you.
So this is the product of some conversation between the armors target, which is up to this year
in the kind of work of this culture, which is a very high regard.
There's the same spot, as well as as far as the market, the more appropriate place,
and more accessible place, would be to have that, there's the hands of the institutional.
We have relatively short time frame to local lists that we've got the other mankind,
the market, the market, and the green, the green, the same amount to the wall.
Probably the greatest confusion in this whole thing was through the mean, or there are a number
of different tracks at public land.
But what you had to do with that is one of the tracks that you took through.
And the part of the market is the green, the terms of that.
I think you're here to go to the local community.
the city and the Department of Parliament personally that to do a few programs and to the
cabinet.
Ancillary questions.
Those will sound like it's a great moment with a little bit of an act.
If you want to go back and then I'm going to talk with Chris the channel about it on the other
side of the Department of Parliament and the Department of Parliament is a little bit of an
area of business, and any more space to use, or backwards there.
So, not only is great, but we can use a fairground state, called the SISD's links.
They've not been asked to talk. I think things may just have such great ideas and such opportunities to grow.
But this is a perfect fit to have to not there in an inclusive area, for the kind of outlets,
and the more so than the word, or the English parking, the end, there's been lots of great ideas,
and things you can do around this and help that to it.
I think this is a huge opportunity for the community to support.
I think it's something that everybody's going to do before too.
This is a good thing, because you can post code there, at the very time,
to take the big links and down the house, and you can go get something that's going to put that opportunity in.
So, we're really excited about that.
They've done such a big amount of all of the great and marketing that they've got out there,
and they've got this. They have. So, I hope to see everybody down there.
And I don't want to be afraid to come to you.
The answer to the post, with a part of the park that's been amazing,
being with others and work through.
How we can take this, probably to be happy, and let's give it a second time to the property set up.
So, if we take that property, it wasn't going to be used at this particular time of the week,
we're now going to have people out there attending out there,
instead of the partnership of sitting up and making that,
and helping for all of these things.
They asked us to probably do the information.
It's really a commitment.
And there's asking you to utilize the city manager to enter into your client engagement agreement,
and we're discussing consultations to work with us on a Medicaid to our city, my own person, and policy.
And I said work with us because this will really be a team effort.
The faculty and the whole, they were talking to the involved.
And the staff event would not be finalized until we came back before you worked for the whole,
for the following event.
Our current personal policy has made peace to you over the years,
but we have not had a comprehensive update, and a couple of novels for the leaders, 2015 to 20 years.
The cost of this project is budgeted in this fiscal year budget.
We'll be 16-75 hours, we're taking a closer to 16 hours,
if we've already done some of the work, I should take a closer look to start it.
So when we write our 25,000 dollars, we'll be the maximum of the stance.
I think this is one of the most important things we've got from the past,
because it's a touch of diversity in the world.
And when you get into one of the policies,
usually, if there's an issue in the framework and the framework and the framework,
it's either because policy wasn't very clearly, or generally, or what's not policy.
So with different things that have changed, one of the things we'll be doing is implementing the social media policy,
which we currently have, and we're just looking for things that we think is important
and this is an investment to make sure this is done right and it's done correctly.
Because I've had to do what Tim said, and obviously, in any organization that decides
payroll and personnel, these are one of our greatest expenses,
it's also one of our greatest assets.
Hence, and that's why this is something that's been so important to him,
to end the organization and get right.
And so they're going to bring job length and really solid foundation to give us there.
And having this contract in the place, which really helps so that if I think we're going to bring the right tools
to the program and to get the right to the program.
So I do recommend it to all the work that's done to get us to the program again.
How will they see this project be?
They've really set it up for success.
And I think this is the same thing that you brought to us.
The members, you're ready?
He did it with him, I guess.
And at that time, the council has asked that we work in the process of hiring a city manager.
So we're going to be on board with one of the first things that I talked to know about.
We've done a year and a half of our preparation to get to this point.
And it's been really encouraging to us as we get to that.
And he's 100%.
I'm not asking him to start making that work.
I think we're doing this right on now, we've got to be able to answer that and so I think we're going to do it for you to listen to any questions.
I'll show you.
Thank you.
Good evening.
It's the restaurant bill, ordinance, number CC 2020, bachelor of eight, ordinance of the American City Council of the city environment, and active section.
But 13, that's pretty much the power of the city, so it's probably a little more bill, the motion to reveal any questions that is on that.
I mean, this is going to, we were there to let's attack today, no effect.
This is a silly, I think, commentator, by very strict.
But I don't really like coming out of the, that as far as the city notes and city employees and the billiards, although there's a limit to effects, citizens and the new.
In order to reveal any of those still being stressed and strongly advised,
for the policy to remind everyone, we're a national community goal.
We should remind them of such a distance of what's the most meaningful.
From the employees' minds to the city employees, the notes and city office.
They're going to continue to remind them of policy to the United States, so this does a particularly pretty clear only to the people who are in touch with you.
The bush and the group.
I would just say that the original ordinance was taken from the government's executive committee.
in front of the governor's executive order that at that time,
he's going to place the legacy-protective order,
which he considered on March 12th,
he removed that mass mandate as it relates to the state.
He's going to put it in the mass mandate as the state
of law enforcement city, but it's mandate.
So this is a good idea.
I'd like to thank, hopefully, for the success of the efforts.
I'm like close to the three.
Second.
So, one, two, three, four, four, four.
Same.
Perfect.
At 14, I was doing evidence that any, which is the derivative,
of course on your list of gender,
which draft support.
16, mayor, council, community, community, and mausages.
I would like to pass on congratulations
to our high school and power of the King.
They did something pretty amazing this last week.
They brought one of the five King State Championship.
That's a championship, which, as far as I know, has never been done.
They've got to be tough to repeat that.
But to the kids, to the coaches, to the parents.
They just have to chat with each of all the young big congratulations to them for doing that.
And I hope that I tell them to know a little bit.
I hope that the criminals get in and honor a little bit of comfort.
But I hope that they will do that.
So hopefully, they will be our first meeting in April, and they will have something together.
We can just get in and celebrate and know that.
That huge huge accomplishment.
I don't know if people realize how big it comes to this.
Any family in this day comes big.
But in the five, the one big is amazing.
So, I can grab some of those kids.
And they make it happen in here and celebrate a little bit.
For 17, city-manors, communications.
I think we may have a certain one about the capital and the capital of the several of the projects.
We've got a primary or a major league project.
We all need three closed eyes.
And we're finally getting into the end of our little weather.
Which is what practically impacts our ability to finish that problem.
A major contractor is getting prepared for the service.
And then they should have us raised.
And yes, that's all planned.
He's taking the real, which is all that great.
I think since they have a team, he has folks.
They're hoping that my team will be very determined.
That's all he is and the services will be ready.
And they'll be able to attack that in that area.
and they're going to operate, and then all the way up to the road of tracks,
on the base, on the main street, which is another area.
We're looking very closely at that.
It's a very interesting section there.
We're names of the main street, and I have to go over there.
We'll talk about that a lot today.
This is to be responsible for this, to be able to go down to the city.
So we continue to work with them to get that.
That's very clean up, and it's very, as well as the fact that people sit down,
and do this in a whole pack on it.
In the end, we're just going to make sure that students can't be,
and they can get the final service right down there.
So the end, you know, these last two weeks of March,
it took me a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of all of this,
because it was weather, when I took three of our greats,
but we're weathering, and then we took a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a
bit of a bit of a lot of people.
I'm trying to run, and I'm sure it being that rough, that's really quick,
too.
And I'm trying to be really nice and serve this and build a little shine,
and can be really proud of it.
In the front of the ward, you know, from the first shooting and on south,
he's part of Michael's house and probably gets when he gets even présents.
Kept it.
I got to be, I guess, a very, very excited.
Michael's research, and Michael Nashry, which will also ring you up,
in the experience like greatly, in the United States,
in the United States, in the United States.
So literally, from the public to the public,
to other tracks within the last few days,
make sure you serve us with all the strength.
So I'm really excited about that.
That we can get a microscope to see
which always take place in the main long stretch in the city.
It's not going to be a long process.
I've been right here since I've been trying to figure out
the opportunity in there, the contractor,
and the end is all went for me.
So it's hard to get a time limit
but I'm sure we can smooth it down.
So I didn't see those moving forward.
The other thing I kind of wanted to mention,
that it's capable of taking the people that
didn't know that I guess in the masses.
We have the ability to people that weren't
on the other side.
And so if people go to the city website
and they don't know what to tell me about that.
They go to the services tab, across the top.
From there you go to the full problem,
which takes you to the request track and page.
You scroll them to the public, the link for it.
You're specifying the information there,
and the connection.
Specifically, it's a specified location for the location.
And the point is, Kevin is totally different.
That way, once the city gets out of the course,
the end, somebody goes out,
and who's going to be in the hiding place.
The final, the end is a prioritized and serivational risk.
So a bigger release of the boundaries
with the image of the screen is a final,
a higher priority.
So it's not that it's just very comfortable showing.
based on the risk of the public, so I'm excited.
We certainly encourage people to go down and use that.
And that was a bit of a lot of stuff.
And I hope we can see from all the weather that we're living there.
Next, I'd like to take you to a new home on the situation of the pool.
The team is continuing to work very hard on the pool prep, and you can learn a little.
We're still waiting for a very short of the pool to stay.
That's what we can say about department.
They will also be the ones that are moving to the pool.
Putting them in the liner.
You ever have a bit of tips that we can see from the contractor.
Whether it's nice to know that.
So if you're building those tips in the clinic, third of this month.
That really gives me that point of the scope and cost of the project in the time.
So to kind of have those elements all in the end.
The better to stay.
You have a contract.
So the prize.
You're not really sure about the time to go away.
But the time which we encounter that we've got all those elements in place.
And then we might actually deal with the results of the pool.
If the wind.
Then we'll have to back through that.
And talk to the players.
We're in a regular hiring and training staff.
And so we'll try to get ready to see somebody.
And see somebody.
They're going to have done that.
So hopefully all these years haven't worked in that area in the job.
We used to take a picture back out for some of these years.
We're going to play to our public pool.
A lot of years ago there was a man in the pool.
He had to keep me up there.
He said.
That's always the part of things.
He also had some unexpected damage from the cold weather.
The morning we didn't have so cold as we were going to remember.
And not in the end of the house and the building.
I just, you know, don't remember.
The computer has continued.
And the same time when I came to the show.
But talk earlier.
And it's a couple of seconds.
You better show me.
So that's something we're going to talk about now.
And we're going to talk about it.
And we're going to see a memory of opportunities.
So here in the city, we have a file or our RBA or the pressure of public systems.
We filed the initial peak of make work.
And we had the permission to leave the building.
So we're going to try to help our doctor.
I'm going to make sure that we can cover the new work for the solutions.
That's going to be a success.
That's always cheap.
And we're going to break up.
And we're going to cover up to make sure that we can cover up.
Vince, do we have kind of a last meeting, I think I mentioned Joel Ashburn cleanup,
so I kind of will do that again because I was here in New York.
This is like, originally happened in the year of New York,
based in the big church collection around again in northwest and southwest sections of the city.
That collection was started seven eight annual March 22nd.
In the northeast and southeast section of the city,
the city was started seven eight annual March 22nd.
People think they were never listening to click this.
This is the next to the church in the close to the hospital,
where you are near the castle years,
and when the mailbox is calling cards, park cards,
trade restrictions and bills,
we do not accept any hazardous waste.
Fair physician's degrees for refrigerator to dust that depression and mood,
and no construction degree would be during the entire,
or not attached to the rim will be accepted to the rims,
to the tires and the rims.
In the middle of the evening, back in the last year,
we fixed up, we are in 163 tons in spring evening.
For you know, she can be tons of waste.
So, all the way to the city,
we gathered up, because everybody said that as a driver,
we've got it out of it.
So, this is a very successful program.
And again, I'd like to see this.
I think I couldn't speak that number,
but I think it should be done.
I'm going to see that.
If anybody has any questions, you can call the Salvation Department at 908,
5401, 20608.
So, again, the first spring evening.
Last week, I'm really excited
to be performing all this spring evening.
The employee recognition evening,
will work as a walk in my shoes and walk.
And I'm impressed when you're coming to me.
So, as you can see, the picture is up there,
as I've been through this.
This is a fourth year.
This one, where I've been given.
The inspiration for this award, is when police officers,
their smarts paid for the system shoes to walk.
The award is given to employee who goes about the amount.
In the evening, as we do services,
in the evening spirit of the walk in city police.
This year, we had six employees nominated.
Those employees were the Jim Boyd,
taking away from Tracy Gordon,
Ronald Parker,
Ralph Parker,
in the English Department.
And I'm certainly very proud of the news
that this year's winner for Christmas evening,
was Jim Boyd,
from the solid waste of the opportunity.
So, Jim is even black for a hundred dollars,
as the winner for the name of all sorts.
and the things that are holding, the employee recognition, many of the surprise her with the private pool, a big check,
the balloons and flowers and all of the gym was nominated for a amazing holiday in this place,
which are holding pictures that you see in here.
She basically collect all of this material in solid ways in this hall,
stuff that's being thrown away, but she sets decorations aside as they come out.
I mean, you should construct a very elaborate display of their shoulders and maybe it turns out.
And so, we're just a homer.
So, it's all, it's interesting, it's designed to give,
for these and minimal reasons, she's a representative of the community's spirit, and also the animals.
So, again, congratulations to Jan K. Tracy, Robert Bauer, the neighbor,
for an absolutely great job, very well done.
And thanks for representing all of us.
I think that's Eric, or maybe I can buy this.
I think it's probably the love of the way you can do it at home.
I don't want to talk to you about that sort of thing.
Does anybody have any questions for you?
I don't have any questions about it.
I don't have any questions, but I'd like to comment on Jan,
and I work indirectly with her, for the time being, she's a dream to work with, she's super nice.
She doesn't have a way to do it about what she can, and I just appreciate her.
I don't have to say anything about it.
I don't want to say back to you about A Street.
Of course, it's within a lot of comments about A Street,
and it was kind of a kind of a shame that the baby would say,
or else they would say, and so today I was going by,
and it's all there in their work, and so I stopped.
There's a little live video show people that was there.
And a lot of people think that you mean,
but I didn't get that moment in their crew,
you know, she didn't wear out there around a machine,
and she didn't know about what those guys, what they're tells of.
And I'm actually going to have an A Street,
that went over all the trucker out there for this business.
You know, the guy who you think, or get into this crew,
so I appreciate that.
They're really, really hard to try to fill in with these bottles of bottles,
but with the snow and rain, it's just hard for them to keep them up all the way.
So I've been very impressed.
It's obviously the weather that we've had,
and the bottles that we've caught up with, too.
Like, almost I haven't seen one more than a day.
There's just kind of a block of cracks,
and it's very, isn't cold in that,
and it's been very present to see how quickly it comes out,
it's panicked to the side.
You know, they take calls, they take to females,
and take the online calls, and we'll spend a minute.
They're trying to, and it's paying taxes.
They are, and there's some, and we call them in the process, so.
If somebody's got one out there that they're speaking,
that doesn't really need to be in the intention,
it's probably going to be a really nice to hear it.
So people need to absolutely make sure that they're
thinking about the true and the way they're supposed to do it.
Well, of course, my head from the union was,
if they go out back home, online, how often is that gathering?
How fast is that I'm seeing it?
Well, I think it's pretty good to be.
It's three of us can email, check, whatever.
And then, immediately, once they're acknowledged,
can we be closing that?
So, okay.
And again, it's based on the list.
So, you know, obviously, a model that's bigger than the structure
it is, it's going to take a dynamic.
There's one that's been a gauge of Twitter.
Those that are shallow, and less of a problem,
that they're not trying to try to do it, but, again, that's the right way
to do it, that's the right way to do it, that's the right way to do it.
So, we're going to do something about it.
I don't know whether you will make a guess for that.
I'm trying to take it to the website.
So, we're going to make a guess for that website.
So, I simply said, well, I don't know if you've got any.
Yeah, they're not.
Yeah.
I don't know if you've got any.
The first one.
The guy is, that's great.
Well, a lot of people didn't know it was there.
Yeah.
So, the lab is going to get it right out of the set.
That's what it is.
We're going to do that.
It's not.
We're going to do it.